[{"answer": "We've increased our sales four to five times.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 15, "question": "Jeremy, how has business been in this gun store since the Sandy Hook massacre?", "qSentId": 14}, {"answer": "So I can't speak for any other state but Texas.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 21, "question": "Why are people reacting to such an appalling massacre are raising out to buy more guns and ammunition?", "qSentId": 20}, {"answer": "Your home.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 28, "question": "For self-defense for your home or self-defense of your property?", "qSentId": 27}, {"answer": "I do not.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "Do you believe any guns should be banned?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "It's not guns that kill people.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "In the hands of the right people, yes, yes.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "But do you believe that the more guns there are in America the safer the country is?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "Let's start with the JP Enterprises, semiautomatic, AR- 15.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "And what are we going to start with?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "And this is the pure unmodified semiautomatic?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "I have to try to flip it into an automatic?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "It's a bog standard, if you like, AR-15?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "Yes, it is.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "And that's perfectly legal?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "Correct.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "So all of this is perfectly legal to any American who is not a felon or has a history of mental illness?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "Well, you know, with reload, maybe 60 rounds or so.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "Somebody who knows really what they're doing, how many rounds could they fire in, say, a minute with one of these?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "LCEDE: The -- the true cyclical rate if you had unlimited magazine, then it could shoot about 400 rounds a minute.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "Sorry?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "If I had to guess.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "Two hundred?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "For law-abiding citizens, I think it's an excellent idea.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "Do you think that's a good idea?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "That's the only difference.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "And that's the only difference?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "Well, you have to have drill well the inside of a receiver, of course you have to have the right receive.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "How sophisticated is it -- I mean, how difficult is it for somebody who knows what they're doing to take an AR-15 and make it like an automatic?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "Yes, they can.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "But the parts can be bought legally?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "You can.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "You could buy them separately?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "Well, no.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "But if you're in a confined area like a movie theater, you don't really care, right?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "LCEDE: Slide Fire Stock.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "And the guy -- the guy at Aurora used an AR-15 and I think he had what's called a slider device?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "It allows the weapon -- it's even less accurate than this and it's really hard to actually shoot.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "What does that do to an AR-15?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "Well, technically it shoots about 650 rounds a minute.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "How many bullets does it allow you to fire?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "And you sell them here?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "For me in the home, what people are talking about is, you know, the way this world is going that the military and United Nations are going to come in and try to take our guns.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "Of all the arguments to have one of these, home defense is probably the least plausible from your point of view?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "Do you really believe that?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "I would hope not, but if it's an executive order --", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "Can you imagine U.S. Marines charging on to your property and try to steal your guns?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "If they're forced to.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "But do you think the American military would attack its own people?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "They want it because they are law-abiding citizens and they know it's legal to purchase it now and it won't be legal later.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "And do you think that's what many Texans feel about why they would need a weapon like this?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "Easy to use?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "These run anywhere from $25,000 to $45,000, depends on the make and model.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "What will it cost me?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "It's about 900 rounds a minute.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "What is the rate of fire of one of these?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "You sit like this.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "OK?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "This is an investment.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "Why would any civilian want -- need one of these?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "You could.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "I could buy that from you?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "Well, it seems to be more show than reality because it seems like on the very same day the majority leader came out and said that they're not going to pass any assault weapons ban.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "What was your reaction to what he said?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "No, the problem that we have with regard to the background checks is that current background checks are not working.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "Do you support 100 percent background checks -- universal background checks?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "Well, the principle of ensuring that criminals and those who have mental issues do not get their hands on guns are very important.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "In principle -- in principle of universal background checks, do you support that?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "What we need to do is enforce the laws and take measures to crack down on violence, to help those with mental challenges, to put the criminals behind bars and prevent criminals from getting a hold of guns in the first place.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "Can you guarantee that?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "Absolutely not.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "Would you support a ban on magazines that have more than 10 rounds?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "Because look at the Texas border itself.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "But has any Texas rancher, to your knowledge, ever been confronted with a Mexican drug cartel?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "Every month you'll have --", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "When?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "With Mexican drug cartels and Texan farmers?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "Do you agree with the fact that you can't legally buy, in most places in America, machine guns, you know, warfare style machine guns?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "Well, that's a ban that's in place.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "Do you support that?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "We have been fined with that ban.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "Do you support it?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "However --", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "Why do you -- why doesn't that breach your constitutional rights?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "Well, first, I think that any Texan has a right to be able to purchase one of those weapons.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "What is your definition of an assault rifle, given I can legally buy that here and kill 300 people in one minute?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "I didn't -- I still -- I guess I'm still in total disbelief that Chris is gone.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "What did you feel when you heard about this in terms of what Chris was trying to achieve?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "Against a lot of things.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "But against what?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "The guy who put a gun to my head -- have you ever had a gun to your head?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "Have you ever had a man look you in the eyes and say I'm going to blow your head off?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "You're missing the point of what I'm saying.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "Why would you have needed an AR-15 in that situation?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "No, I don't fear tyranny.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "Do you fear tyranny, genuinely?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "It was limited looting.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "Were they looting?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "Simple.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "What is your answer to the parents of Sandy Hook who had their children blown to pieces about how you are personally, through the instrument of your radio show, going to try and make America a safer place than it was?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "Either one.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "Armed teachers or armed guards?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "Do I believe that the NRA agrees with -- I don't know what the NRA agrees with me or not.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "Do you believe the NRA agrees with this?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "It worked out.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "Am I wrong?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "You have actually people in your country that decided long ago that they didn't want to have one man over an entire nation.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "What did we change?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "Let's get back to this issue.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "Am I wrong?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "Because we have armed guards.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "Let me ask you, do you know why there are no shootings on planes in America?", "qSentId": 586}, {"answer": "That is my understanding.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "Is that your understanding?", "qSentId": 617}, {"answer": "Firing weapons like that that are incredibly powerful, I've never really done it before.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 651, "question": "Wasn't that fun?", "qSentId": 650}, {"answer": "Well, a number of things.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 671, "question": "If the answer isn't very convincing, why the least we couldn't do to those poor families who lost people to that weapon is not just remove those from the equation?", "qSentId": 670}, {"answer": "You don't understand that it's a simple inanimate tool that tens of millions of American families own, that have never caused a problem, never had an accident and will never commit a crime.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 677, "question": "What don't I understand?", "qSentId": 676}, {"answer": "You are so full of crap.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 682, "question": "It's not a minor aberration?", "qSentId": 681}, {"answer": "I care about all death.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 696, "question": "Do you care about murders or do you only care about murders with guns?", "qSentId": 695}, {"answer": "Well, I think I can frame it best by identifying the scammer in chief who claims that just to save one life would be worth this.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 729, "question": "Which of his proposals do you agree with?", "qSentId": 728}, {"answer": "He had a chance to save four American lives in Benghazi and refused to do so.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 731, "question": "Isn't it worth it?", "qSentId": 730}, {"answer": "Absolutely not.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 738, "question": "ORGAN: Do you agree with universal background checks?", "qSentId": 737}, {"answer": "Because the government doesn't need to know who has what.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 740, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 739}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 761, "question": "Do you think America is going to be safer because gun stores like this are selling so furiously and so much faster weapons and ammunition, increasing both in America?", "qSentId": 760}, {"answer": "America and Switzerland, I believe.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 772, "question": "Do you know the two countries which have the highest per capita rate of firearms per civilian?", "qSentId": 771}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 774, "question": "No, do you know what the second one is after America?", "qSentId": 773}, {"answer": "Let me give you some countries, Australia, Britain, Japan, Canada.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 784, "question": "A gun free zone in all these cities where the slaughter rate is the highest of anywhere, including Yemen?", "qSentId": 783}, {"answer": "I wouldn't want you in a tank.", "docId": "130204pmt", "aSentId": 789, "question": "Are you sure of that?", "qSentId": 788}]